BLAKE GILLANDERS

- **♀** 52a aranui road , Mapua, 7005, Tasman, New Zealand
- ☑ blakegillanders@gmail.com
- **** 02108154626

PERSONAL STATEMENT

After leaving school i had a few years of work experience with MacLab where I worked In a variety of jobs with engineers, labourers and worked with the office a bit this work was good at the time it taught me some very valuable skills. From there i moved to van and a man where I'm currently working and working towards my class two license it's made me realize that this sort of work isn't for me and I want to start working towards getting qualified in a field that I've always had a passion for which is working in IT. So in july of 2023 I started working towards my bachelors degree at NMIT.

WORK HISTORY

MacLab

Nelson, NewZealand Jul 2023 - Present

NZ POST

Nelson, New Zealand Jan 2023 - Present

Van and a man

Nelson, New Zealand Nov 2022 - Apr 2023

MacLab

Nelson, New Zealand Apr 2022 - Present

Maclab

Nelson, New zealand Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

MacLab (NZ) Ltd

Nelson, New Zealand Jul 2021 - Jan 2022

MacLab

Nelson, New Zealand Nov 2020 - Jul 2021

Yard Worker

I'm currently working part time for MacLab LTD at the Nelson port working a casual contract doing 3-5 hours of work Monday to Friday I work putting cotton sleeves onto pvc tubes for the mussel boats to use with mussel rope

• Forklift Operator

Delivery driver

I work every sunday at NZ post deliver "my food bag" food boxes while I study for my bachelors degree

- Driving a Manual HiAce
- Van maintaince checks daily

Class 1 truck driver and furniture mover

Full time work training up for my class 2 license

- Driving class 1 trucks
- Load safety and security
- customer service

Yard hand

Im currently working as a yard hand at maclab working 10-11 hour days operating a rope pulling machine, driving a forklift and cutting up mussel floats

General factory hand

Engineering labourer

I started off by helping to remove an impingement freezer where I learnt to use power tools. After the freezer removal was completed I learnt more engineering skills including experience welding with both a TIG and arc welder. I completed a number of small projects and carried out repairs in the factory, some of these were mostly unsupervised.

General factory hand

QUALIFICATIONS

NMIT

Nelson, New Zealand 2023 - Present

Bachelor of IT

I have just started my study on july 17th 2023 at NMIT doing my bachelors of IT

NCEA Level 2

Nelson, New Zealand 2020

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Tech sawy/ Experienced with computers, computer programs and other• Full class 1 license electronic devices
- Power tools. Handheld and some fixed
- Learner class 2 license

- Welding experience on both TIG and ARC welders
- Forklift OSH certificate
- Basic html coding skills

PERSONAL SKILLS

Time Management

I always monitor time to make sure I go where I'm needed 5-10 minutes early

Positive attitude

I always show up to work with a positive attitude looking forward to the day ahead even if the work isn't great

Work Ethic

I take pride in doing my work correctly and efficiently.

INTERESTS

- Computers/technology
- Learning new skills
- Fishing

- Fitness/Running
- Weightlifting

REFEREES

Andrew Harvey

Head Engineer - MacLab

☑ andrew.harvey@maclab.co.nz

• 0272277000

Nick carter

Supervisor - Mac lab

• 0210621212

Pallas Andrew

Full time Contractor - NZ POST

☑ Pallasavandrew@gmail.com

C 021689830

Gary Rountree

CFO - Mac-Lab

☑ gary.rountree@maclab.co.nz

C 0272139530

Jonny lewis

Operations manager - Van and man

C 0221906181